I'm sure Alejandro will love this.
We're reservado for the day.
It's my grandson's birthday.
Hmm?
You're making the sushi cry.
The Old Chef
of México
Señor Guillermo.
Can't you hear their hoarse pleas?
T-The Sushi Police!
This is an affront to sushi...
Nay, an abomination!
You've got it all wrong!
It's for my grandson's birthd—
Birthday or not, sushi with strawberries
and chili sauce is outrageous!
It's delicioso, you know!
Now! No time to waste!
I'm here for some sushi!
Sanitation soy sauce laser cannon
Perdon, Alejandro...
Your shop's closed for good.
What have you done?
We had good memories at that place!
It sounds like they're really pissed off.
Mysterious Masked Luchador (Kawasaki)
Geronimo!
¡Muchas gracias!
They ran away!
You wrecked Abuelito's shop!
Alejandro...
Bull's-eye.
Sushi is stupid anyway!
Sushi
Police
Head
quarters
Are we really doing the right thing?
C'mon, pull it out!
Spin-spin-spin-spin...
Ow!
T-Thank you!
Secretary to the WFCO Director-General, Madam Fuji.
Madam Fuji.
We've completed our mission.
How come the secretary's a cat?
Surely you kid.
Shh, we don't talk about that.
The Director-General wants to speak to us directly?
Men, how are your injuries?
I can handle this much for the crying sushi all over the world.
WFCO Director-General, Carlos Tanaka
In every era, the righteous have been victims of persecution.
I am well aware.
Here are your new orders.
Investigate this woman.
She's the one who...
Her name is...
Sarah Bynes.
I
don't
under
stand
you
I
don't
under
stand
you
Sushi Trivia
I
don't
under
stand
you
I
don't
Sushi Trivia
under
A sushi roll is
all about the "nori".
under
A sushi roll is
all about the "nori".
stand
you
A sushi roll is
all about the "nori".
Nori was first cultivated in the Edo period,
when Shinagawa fishermen discovered seaweed
growing on their fish traps.
Nori was first cultivated in the Edo period,
when Shinagawa fishermen discovered seaweed
growing on their fish traps.
Nori was first cultivated in the Edo period,
when Shinagawa fishermen discovered seaweed
growing on their fish traps.
Nori was first cultivated in the Edo period,
when Shinagawa fishermen discovered seaweed
growing on their fish traps.
I
don't
under
stand
you
I
don't
under
stand
you
Nori was first cultivated in the Edo period,
when Shinagawa fishermen discovered seaweed
growing on their fish traps.
Nori was first cultivated in the Edo period,
when Shinagawa fishermen discovered seaweed
growing on their fish traps.
Nori was first cultivated in the Edo period,
when Shinagawa fishermen discovered seaweed
growing on their fish traps.
Nori was first cultivated in the Edo period,
when Shinagawa fishermen discovered seaweed
growing on their fish traps.
After some creative efforts, the
Edo delicacy "Asakusa nori" was born.
I
don't
under
stand
you
I
don't
under
stand
you
After some creative efforts, the
Edo delicacy "Asakusa nori" was born.
Tenchou Fansubs