Someone...
Help us...
Please...
I hear the sushi crying for help again.
Turning to port!
Freeze! This is the Sushi Police!
A Premises Search
with Pride on the Line
As you can see, we only make authentic sushi.
Isn't that right, Jean?
Oui.
Did we mess up, Mr. Honda?
Can't you two hear their hoarse pleas?
Non non non...
You're not serving up monkey rolls, are you?
Under the Sushi Protection Act, Article VII,
this falls under an offense for confectionary additives.
There's no way we would make such terrible sushi!
And just what is this, then?
That's soy sauce.
Kawasaki.
Open it!
What's the magic word?
Open it, please.
Stop! Don't do it!
This is chocolate spread, isn't it?
Merde!
Jean!
Oui!
They even have a grill for yakitori?!
Non!
Nobody make a move!
Or this precious Uonuma koshihikari gets it!
You coward, taking the rice hostage...
Don't think you can fool me.
This is Thai rice!
Mai pen rai!
Damn it!
Merde!
Don't the French take pride in its own nation's culture?
Why would you do this?
Look around you.
There's less demand for French cuisine by the day.
Its rich flavors made with decadent cream and butter...
No one's looking for that now.
The world's gone healthy, after all.
Sushi didn't become popular worldwide because it's healthy!
It's because authentic sushi is the most delicious food in the world!
We'll be taking your sign now!
Maman...
Did the sushi place go out of business?
If it's authentic sushi you want, please visit these shops.
Do they have monkey rolls there?
The Sushi Police.
Until the day authentic sushi has spread around the world...
We will continue to fight.
I
don't
under
stand
you
I
don't
under
stand
you
Sushi Trivia
I
don't
under
stand
you
I
don't
under
Sushi Trivia
stand
The vinegared rice used in
sushi is known as "shari".
stand
you
I
don't
under
stand
you
The vinegared rice used in
sushi is known as "shari".
I
Vinegar has a characteristic flavor,
and also acts as a great preservative,
preventing cooled rice from hardening.
Vinegar has a characteristic flavor,
and also acts as a great preservative,
preventing cooled rice from hardening.
Vinegar has a characteristic flavor,
and also acts as a great preservative,
preventing cooled rice from hardening.
I
don't
under
stand
you
Vinegar has a characteristic flavor,
and also acts as a great preservative,
preventing cooled rice from hardening.
Vinegar has a characteristic flavor,
and also acts as a great preservative,
preventing cooled rice from hardening.
Vinegar has a characteristic flavor,
and also acts as a great preservative,
preventing cooled rice from hardening.
Because it lets sushi artisans display their tastes and skills, there are even places that say "a sushi shop is all about its rice".
I
don't
under
stand
you
I
don't
under
stand
you
Because it lets sushi artisans display their tastes and skills, there are even places that say "a sushi shop is all about its rice".
Tenchou Fansubs