This rocket fishing boat is like an embassy.
So this counts as illegal entry into Japan...
Director-General Carlos...
Like I said, this counts as illegal...
Hey, is Carlos on this ship?
We've never met the Director-General in person.
How do you get orders from him, then?
M-M-M-Mr. Honda would know!
Interrogation
Room
Hey, what can I do for you?
The Sushi Interrogation of Sarah
Welcome...
Miss Sarah.
We'll question you now on suspicions of espionage.
Why did you trespass on this ship?
Where's the milk and sugar?
The what now?
You serve tea with milk and sugar.
At least overseas.
Well, we're in Japan!
Here ya go, milk and sugar!
Don't bring it out, you dolt!
It shouldn't matter how you eat sushi, anyway.
Don't give me that.
Deep down, you like authentic sushi, don't you?
If you didn't, you wouldn't have gone straight for the ginger!
Kawasaki!
Inauthentic garnishes around the world
Pickles, kimchi, lemon, and lettuce!
They don't get the point of the pickled ginger!
It's just ginger in sugar and vinegar, isn't it?
The ginger's tartness cleanses the palate!
So do the pickes, right?
Ginger has antiseptic properties!
Can't you hear the insulted ginger crying?!
I know you appreciate authentic sushi, so stop interfering.
It isn't much but...
This sushi's made with fish shipped fresh from Tsukiji!
This would run you 30 grand in Ginza.
Are you trying to bribe me?
Why, I would never.
But you can hear them too, can't you?
The joyous cries of this sushi, that is!
Eat me! C'mon, eat me!
I'm really tasty! Eat me!
Hurry up, eat me!
Eat me! C'mon, eat me!
She saw through it?!
Sushi Police, you're rotten through and through!
A pair of chopsticks can't scratch this ship!
Suzuki!
Grab ahold of this Tochigi kanpyo!
Kanpyo?!
I love Japanese sushi!
But I hate what you're doing!
Free sushi...
Thank God for that kanpyo...
She couldn't have done that unless she knew how
extremely durable striped ebony chopsticks are.
Could it be that woman has a past in Japan?
I
don't
under
stand
you
I
don't
under
stand
you
Sushi Trivia
I
don't
under
stand
you
I
don't
Sushi Trivia
There is a reason why the teacups at
sushi restaurants are so large.
under
There is a reason why the teacups at
sushi restaurants are so large.
under
There is a reason why the teacups at
sushi restaurants are so large.
stand
you
There is a reason why the teacups at
sushi restaurants are so large.
A long time ago, when sushi was served at stalls,
a single chef would need to do everything.
I
don't
under
stand
you
A long time ago, when sushi was served at stalls,
a single chef would need to do everything.
I
don't
under
stand
you
A long time ago, when sushi was served at stalls,
a single chef would need to do everything.
So that he would not need to give refills,
the logical choice to use large teacups was made.
I
don't
under
stand
you
I
don't
under
stand
you
So that he would not need to give refills,
the logical choice to use large teacups was made.
you
So that he would not need to give refills,
the logical choice to use large teacups was made.
Tenchou Fansubs